caultimates.com 2015-06-23

# Privacy Policy - CA CMA CS Exam News

The most important factor at caultimates.com  is our visitor’s privacy policy. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

This Privacy Policy is updated or  revised from time to time. You can revisit it regularly.

### We use Log Files

We use log files like below. The information in the log files includes:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Internet browsers
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks
  * Referral links
  * External links

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

### We use Cookies

  * We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience.
  * Caultimates.com  has no access or control over third-party advertiser’s cookies.
  * You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.
  * If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options.
  * Instructions for doing so and for another cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.
  * See below for other Adverts and Sponsored links policy.

### Email Newsletter

  * This blog operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about regular updates,notifications,news,amendments  and services supplied by this blog.
  * Users can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion.
  * Some subscriptions may be manually processed with the newsletter subscribers.
  * All personal details relating to subscriptions are held securely .
  * No personal details are passed on to third parties nor shared with companies / people outside of the company that operates this website.

### External Links

  * Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links users should always adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this blog.
  * The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts.
  * Users should note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

### Adverts and Sponsored Links

  * This website may contain sponsored links and adverts. These will typically be served through our advertising partners, to whom may have detailed privacy policies relating directly to the adverts they serve.
  * Clicking on any such adverts will send you to the advertiser’s website through a referral program which may use cookies and will track the number of referrals sent from this website.
  * This may include the use of cookies which may in turn be saved on your computers hard drive.
  * Users should note they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

### Social Media Platforms

  * Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this blog and it’s owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.
  * Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details.
  * This blog, nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.
  * This blog may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question.
  * Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.
  * We will never share illegal or pornographic or adult content in our social media platforms.

### Shortened Links in Social Media

  * This blog and it’s owners through their social media platform accounts may share web links to relevant web pages.
  * By default some social media platforms shorten lengthy url’s [web addresses] (Example : <http://wp.me/p48UlR-47>).
  * Users are advised to take caution and good judgement before clicking any shortened url’s published on social media platforms by this blog  and it’s owners.
  * Despite the best efforts to ensure only genuine url’s are published many social media platforms are prone to spam and hacking and therefore this website and it’s owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any shortened links.

### Contact & Communication

  * Users contacting this blog and/or it’s owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use.
  * Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.
  * Users can contact us using giving contact form. ( or ) click [www.caultimates.com/contact](http://www.caultimates.com/contact) .
  * Users can follow our blog at various social media platforms which are mentioned  
below :

  1. Facebook page : [www.facebook.com/caultimatespage](http://www.facebook.com/caultimatespage)  .
  2. Facebook group : [www.facebook.com/groups/caultimates](http://www.facebook.com/groups/caultimates)
  3. Twitter : [www.twitter.com/caultimates](http://www.twitter.com/caultimates)
  4. Youtube : [www.youtube.com/caultimates](http://www.youtube.com/caultimates)
  5. Google+ : [www.google.com/+Caultimates](https://www.google.com/+Caultimates)
  6. Or mail at [admin@caultimates.com](mailto:admin@caultimates.com)

This Privacy policy last updated on **11/02/2014** .
